{
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {
            "question": "What is Linux?",
            "correct_answer": "Kernel",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Driver",
                "OS",
                "Server"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How to change directory?",
            "correct_answer": "cd",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "dir",
                "cp",
                "cd ."
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How to remove files?",
            "correct_answer": "rm",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "remove",
                "rmf",
                "del"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How to list block devices?",
            "correct_answer": "lsblk",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "lsusb",
                "lsdev",
                "ls /dev"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How to see CPU stats?",
            "correct_answer": "lscpu",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "top",
                "htop",
                "lstat"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which command is used to find files?",
            "correct_answer": "find",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "search",
                "lookup",
                "see"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What command is used to connect to server?",
            "correct_answer": "SSH",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "telnet",
                "rsync",
                "http"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Linux requires a license",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What command is used to see permissions?",
            "correct_answer": "ls -al",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "ls -t",
                "ls -a",
                "ls -h"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What command is used to download packages?",
            "correct_answer": "apt",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "yum",
                "dpkg",
                "pacman"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Linux?",
            "correct_answer": "Kernel",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Driver",
                "OS",
                "I don't know!!!!"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How to change directory?",
            "correct_answer": "cd",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "dir",
                "change",
                "cdd"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How to remove files?",
            "correct_answer": "rm",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "remove",
                "rmf",
                "delete"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How to list block devices?",
            "correct_answer": "lsblk",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "lsusb",
                "lsdev",
                "ls /dev"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How to see CPU stats?",
            "correct_answer": "lscpu",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "top",
                "htop",
                "lstat"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which command is used to find files?",
            "correct_answer": "find",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "search",
                "lookup",
                "see"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What command is used to connect to server?",
            "correct_answer": "SSH",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "telnet",
                "rsync",
                "http"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Linux requires a license",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What command is used to see permissions?",
            "correct_answer": "ls -al",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "ls -t",
                "ls -a",
                "ls -h"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What command is used to download packages?",
            "correct_answer": "apt",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "yum",
                "dpkg",
                "pacman"
            ]
        }

    ]
  }